export const cardData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How many knock outs did Ippo have by the time season 2 starts",
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Who was the opponent that Ippo's first lost is accredited too when he's a professional boxer",
    answer: "Dante"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Does Ippo consider himself a Challenger or a Champion while he holds the Japan Feather Weight Champion Belt",
    answer: "Challenger"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Who is Ippo boxing rival throughout season 1 and 2",
    answer: "Ichiro Miyata"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who inspired Ippo to box",
    answer: "Takamura"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Why does Ippo box",
    answer: "Because its fun/ To know what true strength is"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Who is Ippo's love interest",
    answer: "Kumi Mashiba"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "in the anime what character is it joked that Ippo has a homosexual crush on",
    answer: "Ichiro Miyata"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Who was Ippo's first match against in the Eastern Japan Feather Weight Rookie Championship",
    answer: "Jason Osma"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who is Ippo's main rival in Strength",
    answer: "Sendo"
  },
]; 